douknow.com 2013-10-30

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Do You Know Inc. ( **“DYK”** , **“we”** or **“us”** ) operates a social networking service by the name of _DoUKnow?_ **** ( **“ _DoUKnow?”_ **or the **“Service”** ), that allows members to communicate with one another through the sharing of member-generated content and member-supplied information.  We have created this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information.        
This Privacy Policy applies only to the information that you provide to us.  It explains what data we collect from you and how we use it, share it, and safeguard it.  By using our Service, you are accepting and agreeing to the policies and practices set forth in this Privacy Policy and in our Terms and Conditions.  Any privacy-related dispute will be governed by this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.  
For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, **“personal information”** means information that can identify an individual directly or through other reasonably available means.  The meaning of “personal information” shall be interpreted in a manner that conforms with the minimum requirements of applicable provincial and federal privacy legislation.  
The Service is not available to individuals who are younger than 13 years old.  If you are younger than 13 years old, please do not provide us with any of your information.    
What Personal Information is Collected?  
The choice to provide us with your personal information is always yours.  However, your decision to withhold particular information may limit our ability to provide you with some of our services.  
DYK receives and stores various types of information about you, as follows:  

**Registration information**

  * _DoUKnow?_ is a social networking tool that operates through the mutual sharing of information.  The Service operates on the assumption that users want to provide and share certain personal information with one another.  We therefore collect some personal information about you when you register with us, namely username and password information, your name, email address, gender, city, province, and country.  We also ask that you complete an “About Me” section, which will appear on your member profile.  All of this information constitutes registration information.  Registration information is used to allow you to set up a member account and profile that can be used to interact with others through the Service. 

**Information You Choose to Share**  
We receive and store any information you enter on our Service or provide to us in any other way.  In addition to registration information, you have the option of providing DYK and its members with additional information, including but not limited to your date of birth, mobile phone number, address, website, and education information.  You may also choose to upload to our website an avatar, or photographs or videos of yourself.  And you may choose to create Super DoUKnow lists, events, and groups, and broadcast status updates.  This information is provided on a voluntary basis and allows you to better interact with other members through the Service.    
We may use your personal information in order to adapt our Service to better serve you and our community.  We may also use your personal information to communicate with you about your use of the Service, as well as to inform you about specials and new features. 

How is Your Personal Information Shared?  

Personal information about our members is an integral part of our business.  _DoUKnow?_ is a social networking tool that facilities the sharing of personal information.  Members voluntarily join the Service to presumably network with others through the sharing of personal information.  Given that the nature of our Service is based on the sharing of information, your username, avatar, gender, date of birth, “About Me” information, mobile phone, address, city, province, country, website, and education information are visible to the public by default.  Note that only your username, gender, city, province, country, and “About Me” information is mandatory in order to use the Service, and that your username must always be public information.

Notwithstanding this default, you have control over the sharing of all of your other information.  The option is yours as to what content and what information you wish to be public, visible only to _DoUKnow?_ Members, visible only to your _DoUKnow?_ Friends, or visible only to you.  Each of these options is explained below.  

**Visible to the Public:** By selecting this option, you acknowledge that your content becomes publicly available information.  This means that anyone, including people who are not registered with DYK, will be able to see it. **   **  

**Visible to _DoUKnow?_ Members:** By selecting this option, you acknowledge that your content is visible to all members of the Service, regardless of whether you know them.  

**Visible to _DoUKnow?_** **Friends:** By selecting this option, you acknowledge that your content is visible only to those individuals who you have chosen to approve as “friends” on the Service.  The content is otherwise not visible to other members of the Service or to the general public.  

**Visible Only to Me:** By selecting this option, you acknowledge that you are providing DYK with content that is personal to you, and you elect to not have such content shared with others.  

If you are uncomfortable with the sharing of your information, please ensure your privacy settings are set for the most privacy protective (so that only your username and avatar, if applicable, are disclosed publicly).  If you are not comfortable with even your username and avatar being public, _DoUKnow?_ , given its design and purpose, may not be appropriate for you.    

Note that, depending on your privacy settings, you may be searchable on the Service by the information you provide.  For example, if you choose to have your email address visible to _DoUKnow?_ members, a member may search you by your email address and request to connect as “friends”.    

You should be aware that persons having access to your content through our Service may use it or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge.  **We therefore urge you to think carefully before you upload any content, or supply any information, that you may deem private.**  

We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone.  We only share your personal information with others in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise notified to you.    

By uploading content to _DoUKnow?_ (e.g. photos, videos), you grant DYK a worldwide, non-exclusive, royalty-free licence to use, copy, distribute, process, adapt, modify, publish, and transmit such uploaded content in any and all media or distribution methods, even where it contains, consists of, or includes content covered by intellectual property rights.  By providing DYK with uploaded content, you grant DYK a right to sublicense and allow DYK to distribute such uploaded content to other companies, organizations or persons who partner with DYK for the syndication, consolidation, broadcast, distribution or publication of such uploaded content.  

Using _DoUKnow?_ Features  

The Service has the following features that may allow you to share your information with others.  Please remember that if you choose to provide personal information using certain features of the Service, that information may be available to the entire _DoUKnow?_ community, or may be published on the _DoUKnow?_ website.  

  * Create a profile
  * Upload a photo (avatar or other)
  * Upload a video
  * “Friend” or “unfriend” other members
  * Be followed by other members
  * Create a Super DoUKnow list
  * Chat with other members and/or connect to Facebook/Gtalk chat programs*
  * Post questions, view and offers replies and opinions in the “Ask” feature  

* Note that any information shared to Facebook and/or Gtalk users, or shared through Facebook and/or Gtalk accounts, is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies of such services, as applicable.    

**Disclosure to Third Parties  
**

We may disclose your personal information to third parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy where you have so consented or in those limited circumstances set out below.   

**Where required or permitted by law**  

The type of information we are legally required to disclose may relate to criminal investigations.  In some instances, such as a legal proceeding or court order, we may also be required to disclose your personal information to authorities.  Only the information specifically requested is disclosed and we take precautions to satisfy ourselves that the authorities that are making the disclosure request have legitimate grounds to do so.    
Your personal information may also be disclosed in situations where we are legally permitted to do so, such as in the course of employing reasonable and legal methods to enforce your rights or to investigate suspicion of unlawful activities.  We may release certain personal information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property and safety of ourselves and others.    
**In the context of a business transfer, bankruptcy or transaction**

  * We may use your personal information and disclose your personal information to third parties in connection with the proposed or actual financing, insuring, sale, securitization, assignment or other disposal of all or part of our business or assets (including accounts) for the purposes of evaluating and/or performing the proposed transaction.  These purposes may include, as examples, permitting such parties to determine whether to proceed or continue with the transaction, fulfilling any reporting or audit requirements to such parties, and/or disclosing personal information as part of concluding a sale or transfer of assets.  Our successors and assigns may collect, use and disclose your personal information for substantially the same purposes as those set out in this Privacy Policy. 

**Where we employ a third party service provider**

  * We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform website-related services, such as maintenance services, database management, and web analytics, or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.  These third parties may have access to your personal information only to perform these tasks on our behalf.  In such instances, we will use contractual or other means to ensure such third parties provide a comparable level of protection over your personal information while it is in their control.    

Except as specifically provided for in this Privacy Policy, we do not disclose any personal information to third parties.  

Email Communications  

We email you with information that we think you will find useful.  Our emails may contain news, products, offers, surveys or promotions related to our Service.  We may email you to inform you of group invitations, friendship requests, and account details.  We also email you notice of changes to our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.  If you do not want to receive commercial email or other mail from us, you can choose the unsubscribe option in the emails we send to you or you can change your account settings.  Please note that, in all cases, you will continue to receive system updates (such as forgotten usernames and passwords) and legal notices from us, such as notices regarding this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.  Those legal notices govern your use of the Service and you are responsible for reviewing them for changes.  Notices will also be posted on our website, and will govern use of the website.  

Security  

_DoUKnow?_ accounts are password-protected for your privacy and security.  We recommend that you select your password carefully and limit access to your computer and browser (e.g. sign off after each use) to prevent unauthorized access to your account and personal information.  

We endeavour to safeguard member information through the employment of reasonable physical, technological, and administrative security measures.  However, no method of transmission of information over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure.  We cannot guarantee the security of member information.   
The Service may contain links to other sites.  DYK is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site, you should read the privacy policy stated on that site. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on the Service.  

Changing or Deleting Your Personal Information  

We make every reasonable effort to keep your personal information as accurate, complete and up-to-date as necessary for the purposes for which it was collected.  You may update certain personal information by visiting the Profile tab on the top of the _DoUKnow?_ website, and by selecting “Edit Profile”.  Personal information is retained only for so long as is reasonably necessary to fulfil the purposes for which it was collected.  
Upon request, you can also access our records of your personal information and challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information and have it amended as appropriate.  Should you identify any incorrect or out-of-date information, DYK will remedy any errors on a reasonable and timely basis.  

Deleting your account permanently removes your account information from _DoUKnow?_.  Should you wish to permanently delete your account, please log in to your account and click on the appropriate link on the “Edit Profile” page.  If you terminate your account, your profile and personal information will be removed from the _DoUKnow?_ site and deleted from our servers.  Note that some of the content that you uploaded (e.g. photos, videos, status updates) may not be deleted upon account deletion.  DYK has no control over content indexed on other websites or search engines, or content that has been shared by you and copied, distributed, re-posted, published or otherwise transmitted by other members.    

Changes to this Privacy Policy  

DYK may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time.  Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used.  If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you by posting an announcement on our Service and/or by sending you an email.  Material changes to the Privacy Policy will be binding thirty (30) days after such changes have been introduced and for which notification of such material changes has been made.  The date when this Privacy Policy was most recently amended is noted at the bottom of the Privacy Policy.     

Our Policy Toward Children  

The Service is not available to individuals who are younger than 13 years old, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.  If we become aware that a child under the age of 13 has registered with our Service or provided us with personal information, we will delete such child’s account and information.  

Children between the ages of 13 and 16 require parental consent to use the Service.  If we become aware that a child between the ages of 13 and 16 has registered with our Service or provided us with personal information absent parental consent, we will delete such child’s account and information.            
If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personal information contrary to the terms of this Privacy Policy, he or she should contact us at info@douknow.com   

Website Governed by this Privacy Policy  

Our website (http://www.douknow.com/) is governed by the provisions and practices stated in this Privacy Policy.  Our website may contain links to third party sites that are not governed by this Privacy Policy.  Although we endeavour to only link to sites that share our commitment to your privacy, please be aware that this Privacy Policy will no longer apply once you leave our website.  We are not responsible for the privacy practices of third party sites.  We therefore suggest that you closely examine the respective privacy policies of third party websites to learn how they collect, use and disclose your personal information.  

Governing Law  

This Privacy Policy, and the handling of personal information, is governed solely by the laws of the Province of Ontario and the federal laws of Canada applicable therein, to the exclusion of any rules of private international law or conflict of laws which would lead to the application of any other laws.  

Members may reside outside of Canada and DYK may perform activities outside of Canada through third parties.  In particular, DYK uses the services of GoDaddy.com, LLC to manage its servers.  As a result, personal information may be stored, processed, or accessed in other countries and may be subject to the laws of those countries.  Information may be disclosed in response to valid demands or requests from government authorities, courts, or law enforcement in those countries.  For example, information that is processed, used, stored or accessed in the United States may be subject to the Patriot Act and applicable anti-terrorism legislation, together with other legislation applicable within the United States.  

Addressing Your Inquiries and Concerns  
We are happy to discuss the content of this Privacy Policy with you and to answer any questions that you may have.  Please direct all questions or enquiries about this Privacy Policy to **info@douknow.com**

Last revised Wednesday, August 8, 2012
